Enrique Marin

Developer & Designer - B.C.S. MX

enriquemarin.vercel.app enrique.marin.h@hotmail.com

+52 612 104 9341



I am a young developer enthusiastic about innovative and technological projects that seek to impact people's lives. In recent years I have worked in areas such as web development and mobile Apps, as well as graphic creation projects such as branding and digital marketing.

Skills

Languages

HTML&CSS *
JavaScript *
Dart *
C#
SQL
NonSQL

Tech / Frameworks

Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Node.js, AdonisJS, MongoDB, MySQL, SQL Server, NGinx, Flutter, Firebase, Android Studio, Git, Visual Studio Code

Design

Illustrator *
Adobe Xd *
Photoshop
After Effects

Idioms

Spanish (native) English (B2)

Experience

Freelance 2020 - Present

Brand Designer, UI Designer & Web Developer

Independent professional focused on development services of web systems, brand design, interface design (UI / UX).

Async Agencia Creativa 2019 – 2020 (13 months)

CoFounder, Designer & Web Developer

Async is an agency dedicated to inpulse companies and entrepreneurs into the digital world through branding, marketing and websites.

Relapp 2019 (6 months)

Brand Designer, UI Designer & App Developer (Flutter)

App sudcalifornian to search all kind of local business and promos in your town.

Cortêz Baja Sur 2018 - 2019 (6 months)

CoFounder, Illustrator & Brand Designer

Clothing brand with a local urban concept that encourages love for Baja California Sur.

JastMedia 2018 – 2019 (2 months)

Front-End Developer, Content Loader

Juniper Data Center's Extending Department Focused on Websites Development for clients in United States

Education

Bachelor in Computing Systems 2018 Tecnológico Nacional de México Campus La Paz

Security & Web Development speciality

wenriquemarin_mx







/enriquemarin

Enrique Marin

Developer & Designer - B.C.S. MX

enriquemarin.vercel.app enrique.marin.h@hotmail.com +52 612 104 9341



Soy un joven desarrollador entusiasta por proyectos innovadores y tecnológicos que busquen impactar la vida de las personas. En los últimos años me he desenvuelto en áreas como desarrollo web y Apps móviles, al igual que proyectos de creación gráfica como branding y marketing digital.

Skills

Lenguajes

HTML&CSS *
JavaScript *
Dart *
C#
SQL
NoSQL

Tech / Frameworks

Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Node.js, AdonisJS, MongoDB, MySQL, SQL Server, NGinx, Flutter, Firebase, Android Studio, Git, Visual Studio Code

Diseño

Illustrator *
Adobe Xd *
Photoshop
After Effects

Idiomas

Español (nativo) Ingles (B2)

Experiencia

Freelance 2020 - Presente

Diseñador de Marca, Diseñador UI y Desarrollador Web

Profesionista independiente enfocado a servicios de desarrollo de sistemas web, diseño de marca, diseño de interfaces (UI / UX).

Async Agencia Creativa 2019 – 2020 (13 meses)
Cofundador, Diseñador y Desarrollador Web

Async es una agencia dedicada a impulsar a empresas y emprendedores dentro del mundo digital a través de branding, marketing y websites.

Relapp 2019 (6 meses)

Diseñador de Marca, Diseñador UI y Desarrollador Móvil

App sudcaliforniana para buscar todo tipo de empresas y promociones de tu localidad.

Cortêz Baja Sur 2018 – 2019 (6 meses) Cofundador, Ilustrador y Diseñador de Marca

Marca de ropa con un concepto local urbano que fomenta el amor hacia Baja California Sur.

JastMedia 2018 – 2019 (6 meses)

Desarrollador Front-End, Content Loader

Departamento que extiende de Juniper Data Center enfocado en el desarrollo de páginas web para clientes en Estados Unidos

Educación

Ing. Sistemas Computacionales 2018
Tecnológico Nacional de México Campus La Paz

Especialidad en Seguridad y Desarrollo Web







/enrique159

